American Chicle Company Records
American Chicle Company Records
- Financial papers
  - American Chicle Company
    - Stock Register, Capital, 1925-1927
    - Sugar Invoices, 1 Envelope, 1947
    - Sundry Accounts, Individuals, 1943-1950; 1952-1963; 11 volumes
    - Transfer Binder, Common Stock, 1924-1925
    - Trial Balance and Work Sheets, 1945-1960; 6 volumes
    - Voucher Record #1, #2, 1914-1916; 2 volumes
  - Calders Company
    - Ledger, 1936
  - Chicle Development Company
    - Bintula Refinery, Ledger, 1950-1952
    - Cash Book, 1948-1957
    - Cash Book, General, 1945-1947
    - Cash Distribution, 1938-1942; 4 volumes
    - Cash Disbursements, General, 1935-1937; 1943-1945,; 1947-1950; 3 volumes
    - Cash Receipts, 1938-1946; 2 volumes
    - Cash Receipts, Special Rubber Acct., 1943-1944
    - Claims, Invoices, 1948-1949
    - Inventories and Balances, 1942-1948
    - Inventories and Balances, Argentina, 1951-1953
    - Journal, General, 1942-1943
    - Ledgers, General, 1942-1943; 1953-1956; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, Barranquilla, 1944
    - Ledger, General, Brazil and Mexico, 1945-1946
    - Ledger, Mexico, Colombia, Rubber Acct., 1943-1944
    - Ledger, Barranquilla, Colombia, Dario and Perillo, 1942-1944
    - Ledger, Colombia, Guatemala, Venezuela, 1945-1946
    - Ledger, Colombia, Libra, Mayor Perielo, 1942-1944
    - Ledger, Dario, Colombia, 1944
    - Ledger, Guatemala and Colombia, 1946-1947
    - Ledger, Mexico, 1939-1941
    - Ledger, Colombia and Guatemala, 1947-1948
    - Ledger, Mexico, Far East, 1944-1945
    - Ledger, Venezuela, 1941-1942
    - Ledger, Guatemala, Nigeria, 1938-1939
    - Ledger, Tower Hill, Nigeria, 1943-1944
    - Ledger, Venezuela, Gum and Rubber, 1943-1944
    - Ledger, Nigeria and Tower Hill, 1941-1942
    - Ledger, Venezuela, Rubber Operations, 1946-1947
    - Ledgers, General, 1939-1950; 7 volumes
    - Ledger, Rubber Plantations, 1942-1943
    - Ledger, Spot Purchases, 1946-1948; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, Spot Purchases, Guatemala, Nigeria, 1948-1950
    - Ledger, General, Mexico, Individuals and Personnel History, 1938-1947
    - Ledger, Spot Purchases, Far East, Nigeria, Panama, and British Honduras, 1945-1946
    - Transfer Binder, 1956-1961
    - Trial Balance, 1939-1945
    - Voucher Register, 1934-1936
    - Delivery Records, Brazil, Br. Honduras, Colombia, Guatemala, Mexico, Nigeria, Panama, Peru, Venezuela, no dates
    - Bankers Trust Company, C.D.C., Special Account, no dates; 2 volumes
    - Journal, 1916-1917
  - Crawford Gum Company
    - Ledger, 1939-1940
  - Frank H. Fleer Company
    - Stock Ledger, no dates
    - Minute Book, 1909
  - Mexican Exploitation Company
    - Cash Books, 1900-1907; 1910; 2 volumes
    - Journals, 1907-1910; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, 1901-1909
  - New York City Transit, Vending
    - Cash Collections, 1951; 1952; 2 volumes
    - Contract, 2nd Year Probable P and L, 1950-1951
    - Contract, 3rd Year Probable P and L, 1951-1952
    - Contract, 4th Year Probable P and, 1952-1953
    - Contract, 5th Year Probable P and L, 1954-1955
    - General Ledger, 1954
    - Vending Ledger, 1955
    - Ledger General #2 Nominal Account, 1950-1951
    - Ledger General #3 Nominal Account, 1949-1951
  - Sen Sen Chiclet Company
    - Cash Book, General, 1913-1914
    - Journal, 1916-1917
    - Journal and Analysis, 1910-1914
    - Journal, Private, 1922
    - Ledger, Capital Stock, 1909-1914
    - Ledgers, Dividend, 1908-1914; 1910; 2 volumes
    - Ledger, Dividend
    - Ledger, Impersonal, 1909
    - Ledger, Private, 1909-1915
    - Ledger, Transfer and Impersonal, 1913-1914
    - Profit and Loss, 1909
    - Purchases and Expenditures, 1909-1914; 1914; 2 volumes
    - Stockholders Listings, 1914
    - Stock Certificates, Cancelled, 1 envelope, 1911
  - Miscellaneous
    - American Chicle Company Journal, 1916-1917
    - Cash, 1916-1917
    - Cash Journal, 1889-1892
    - Chicago warehouse, 1954-1956
    - Stock Ledger, no dates